Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
5582
Kheel Center
80.1 linear ft.
Pamphlets.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The Archives Foreign File is a collection of printed ephemeral documents, issued primarily by foreign and international trade unions and labor organizations. All continents are represented, though the majority of materials is of European origin. Topics covered in this collection include union organizing, unemployment, working conditions, the working class, the labor movement, industrial relations, worker education, international trade unionism, works councils, automation, economic conditions and trends, labor markets, foreign relations, and political movements, including fascism, socialism, and communism. Included in this collection are materials on the World Confederation of Labor and the World Federation of Trade Unions.
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into four sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-79
Boxes 80-81 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
Subjects:
Labor unions; Labor unions--Political activity; Labor unions and foreign policy; Labor movement; International labor activities; Working class; Working class--Education; Industrial relations; Labor market; Unemployment; Economic history; Works councils; Work environment; Management--Employee participation; International relations; Labor unions and communism; Labor unions and socialism; Labor unions and fascism; Industrial safety; Industrial hygiene; Communism; Fascism; Socialism; Automation
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this Collection:
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF)
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF) Section 1: Boxes 1-22
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF) Section 3: Boxes 45-66
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF) Section 4: Boxes 67-79
Boxes 80-82 have not been inventoried at this point.
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 23, Folder: 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Warum es in der UdSSRkeine Arbeitslosigkeit gebenkann, 1948; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Language: German.
  - Item 2: Russia with Our Own Eyes: Full Report of the British Workers Delegation, 1950; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: British Workers' Delegation to the U.S.S.R.
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 3: The Trade Unions, the Party and the State, 1927; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: M.P. Tomskii
  - Item 4: How Russia Gets Output, 1947; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: Robert Bentley Suthers
  - Item 5: Soviet Workers and their Unions: A Reply to the Iron and Steel Trades' Confederation, 1946; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: Ernest E. Thornton
  - Item 6: Soviet Trade Unions: Fifty Questions Answered, 1941; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: Arthur Horner
  - Item 7: Report of the First American Rank & File Labor Delegation to Soviet Russia, 1928; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: American Rank and File Labor Delegation to Soviet Russia
  - Item 8: The Red Whip, 1958; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Soviet Coexistence Strategy: A Case StudyLabor Organization, 1960; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: Alfred Phillip Fenbach
  - Item 10: Lohngestaltung und Gewerkschaften in der Sowjetunion, 1945; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Report of Delegation to the U.S.S.R., 1945; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: Iron and Steel Trades Confederation (Great Britain)
  - Item 12: Trade Unions and Industrial Relations in the Soviet Union, 1958; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: B.C. Roberts
  - Item 13: Soviet Employers in the ILO: The Experience of the 1930s, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: John P. Windmuller
  - Item 14: British Trade Unionists in Moscow: An Eye Witness Account, Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: Henry Levitt
  - Item 15: The Big Smile: An Analysis of the Soviet 'New Look', 1955; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: Matthew Woll
  - Item 16: Organized Labor in the Soviet Union, 1943; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: Edwin Seymour Smith
  - Item 17: Entscheidung von Arbeitskonflikten in der UdSSR, 1950; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: David Vladimirovich Shveitser
- Box: 23, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Trade Union in Soviet Social Insurance: Historical development and Present Functions, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: Gaston V. Rimlinger
  - Item 2: The Trade Unions in Soviet Russia, 1920; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: Independent Labour Party (Great Britain) Information Committee.
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Trade Unions of the USSR, 1951; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: Vsesoiuznyi sezd professionalnykh soiuzov
  - Item 4: Economic Relations between the Soviet Union and Communist China, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: Walter Galenson
  - Item 5: Factory Management and Wages in the Soviet Union (title changed from USSR), 1958; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: Aleksandr Mikhailovich Birman
  - Item 6: Problems of Manpower and Industrialization in the USSR, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: Warren W. Eason
  - Item 7: Science and Politics: The New Sociology in the Soviet Union, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: George Fischer
  - Item 8: Social Security, Incentives, and Controls in the US and USSR, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: The Code of Labor Laws of Soviety Russia // Soviet Russia Pamphlets: The Labor Laws of Soviet Russia, 1920; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: Russian Soviet Government Bureau
    Notes: title change
  - Item 10: The Russian Trade Unions in 1907-1917, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: I.L. Borshchenko
  - Item 11: The Soviet Wage Reform, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Russian Delegation Report, 1953; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Author: Amalgamated Society of Woodworkers
- Box: 23, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Malaya's Biggest Union, 1957; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Malayan Trades Union Congress: What it isThe Future., 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Organized Labor in the Soviet Union, 1943; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The Trade Unions, the Party and the State, 1927; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Economics and Technology: The Case os Soviet Steel, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Author: M. Gardner Clark
  - Item 6: Comparative Wage StructuresSoviet Union and Western Countries, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Role of the Trade Unions in Soviet Society, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: article, outline
  - Item 8: Labor Conditions and Social Security: Labor Disputesand Institutions, 1960; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Author: E. Gershanov, V. Skobelkin
    Notes: article
  - Item 9: Labor Productivity in Soviet and American Industry, 1955; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Collective Agreement for 1974 of the VolgaAutomobile Factory, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Author: Soviet Union
  - Item 11: Study Tour of USSR Steel Industry, October 3-11, 1966: Economic Commission for Europe, Steel Committee -- Chapter IX Labor in the Soviet Steel Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Author: United Nations. Economic Commission for Europe. Steel Committee
  - Item 12: Boris Nicolaevsky 1887-1966, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: The Soviet Fishing Revolution, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Author: Georg Borgstrom
    Notes: article reprinted from Food Technology, 1965, vol. 19, no. 2
  - Item 14: The Soviet Fishing Revolution, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Labor in the Soviet Orbit, 1956; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Author: Anatole Shub
  - Item 16: Text of Draft Directives for DevelopmentFifth Five-Year Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: news paper articles
  - Item 17: Return of the Apparatchik, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Author: Robert Conquest
- Box: 23, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor and the Soviet System, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Author: Romuald Szumski
  - Item 2: Cultural Activities of Soviet Trade Union, 1945; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Author: Llya Tsaregradsky
  - Item 3: Fabrika vykhodit na novye rebezhi, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Author: Anna Andreevna Grinenko
    Language: Russian.
  - Item 4: In Addition to Wages (The Trade Unions and Social Insurance), 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Author: Anatolii Aleksandrovich Shtylko
  - Item 5: Labour Heroism in Soviet Land, 1943; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Author: I.A. Shur
  - Item 6: Muzei Moskovskogo khudozhestvennogo teatra, 1929; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Author: N.D. Teleshov
  - Item 7: The International Labour Movement: The BulletinIndustrial Unions, 1921; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Author: Provisional International Council of Trade and Industrial Unions
  - Item 8: The Third All-Russian Congress of Trade Unions (Resolutions & Regulations), 1920; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Author: Vserossiiskii siezd professionalnykh soiuzov
  - Item 9: Trade Unions in Soviet Russia: A CollectionLabour Research Dept., 1920; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Labor in the Soviet Orbit, 1956; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: The Soviet Trade-Unions During the Period of the Postwar Five-Year Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Author: Vsesoiuznyi tsentralnyi sovet professional'nykh soiuzov
  - Item 12: The Work of the Soviet Trade Unions in the field of social Insurance of the Workers, 1945; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Author: A. Gorbunov
  - Item 13: The Work of the Soviet Trade UnionsInsurance of the Workers, 1945; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Box: 23, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Rise and Fall of the Watusi, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Author: Elspeth Huxley
- Box: 23, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Politica Social del Ministerio de Trabajo, 1955; Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Author: El Salvador. Ministerio de Trabajo y Prevision Social
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 2: Sindicalizacion Racional de los Trabajadores, 1951; Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Author: Ortelio Parra Pradenas
- Box: 23, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: With the !Kung Bushmen: An Account of Mysterious People, 1957; Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: With the !Kung Bushmen: An Account of Mysterious People, 1957; Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Negotiations for a New Agreement in the Transvaal Tobacco Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Report of the National Executive Committee and the National Management Committee submitted to the Twelfth Annual Conference, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Author: Trade Union Council of South Africa
  - Item 5: South Africa in Fact, 1965; Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Author: South African Information Service
  - Item 6: South African Policy and the U.N. Charter, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Author: Hilgard Muller
  - Item 7: The Economic Implications of Political Democracy: The RoadProgress, 1960; Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Author: Sheila T. Van der Horst
  - Item 8: TUCSA Nwesletter No. 45, January/February, 1967; Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: South Africa Prospers while Critics Crumble, 1966; Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Author: H.L.T. Taswell
  - Item 10: South African Prospects and Progress: EconomicIndustrial Giant, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: South African Scope, December 1965, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Box: 23, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Go Forward in Faith: A Statement of the FundamentalRace Relations, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Pictures: South Africa, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Author: South Africa. Dept. of Information
  - Item 3: South African Scope, April 1966: Ethiopia and Liberiain the Hague, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Talking Point: Why You Need a Trade Union, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: TUCSA Fights Communism, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: What TUCSA Means to You, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Why TUCSA Opposes Boycotts and Sanctions, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Box: 23, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Distress in South Wales: Health of Mothers and Babies Imperiled, 1928; Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Author: Parliamentary Labour Party
- Box: 23, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Hungry Viet Workers, 1964; Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: The Labor Movement of South Vietnam, 1968; Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: The Nation, August 30, 1965 (several articles), Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    Notes: serial
- Box: 23, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Rasgos Historicos de la Union General de Trabajadores de Espana, 1953; Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Twenty Years Under the Fascist Dictatorship of General Franco: the lives and Struggles of the Spanish Workers, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Author: World Federation of Trade Unions
  - Item 3: Actividades de la Organizacion Sindical Agraria, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Escuela Sindical Superior de Hosteleria, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Reddacion Definitive de las ConclusionesPlan de Desarrolla, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Desarrolla Sindical, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Financiacion del Pequena y Mediana Empresa, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Historical Factors and the Situation to-day: Vocational Training for Industry in Spain, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Author: Organizacion Sindical. Servicio de Informacion y Publicaciones Sindicales
  - Item 9: Virgen de la Paloma, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Virgen de la Paloma, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Box: 23, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Cooperation at the Level of Undertaking in Spain, 1960; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Author: Eugenio Perez Botija
  - Item 2: La Organizacion Sindical Espanola, 1960; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: La Organizacion Sindical Espanola, 1960; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Legislacion de Seguridad SocialSeguro de Enfermedades Profesionales, 1956; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Sintesis del Sistema de Representacion Sindical en Espana, 1954; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Sintesis del Sistema de Representacion Sindical en Espana, 1954; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Spain: A Summary of Facts, News and Comments on Spanish Affairs, Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Historical Factors and the Situation to-day: Vocational Training for Industry in Spain, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Box: 23, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Rasgos Historicos de la Union General de Trabajadores de Espana, 1953; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Cuaderno de Politica Social, 1954; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Sintesis Estadistica de la Vida Espanola: Agricultura, Producciones, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Sintesis Estadistica de la Vida Espanola: Agricultura, Superficies, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Sintesis Estadistica de la Vida Espanola: Demografia, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Sintesis Estadistica de la Vida Espanola: Energia, Carbon, 1960; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Sintesis Estadistica de la Vida Espanola: Ganaderia, Ganada de Rento, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Sintesis Estadistica de la Vida Espanola: Montes, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Sintesis Estadistica de la Vida Espanola: Trabajo, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Panorama Economico y Social de la Industria Textil Espanola, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Box: 23, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Nuestro Sindicalismo Nacional: glosas en torno a algunos puntos del Fuero del Trabajo, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
    Author: Organizacion Sindical
  - Item 2: Tarifas de Primas Minimas de Accidentes del Trabajo, 1960; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Actividades de la Organizacion Sindical Agraria, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Espana Encadenada, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
    Author: Miguel Sanchez- Mazas
  - Item 5: Historical Factors and the Situation to-day: Vocational Training for Industry in Spain, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: El Parque Sindical Deportivo Puerta de Hierro, 1959; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Box: 23, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Convenios Colectivos Sindicales de Trabajo Legislacion vigente y complementaria con Resoluciones Administrativas, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
    Author: Spain
  - Item 2: Convenios Colectivos Sindicales de Trabajo Legislacion vigente y complementaria con Resoluciones Administrativas, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Documents du Congres, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Situacion Juridica del Trabajador en la Empresa, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
    Author: Spain. Organizacion Sindical Espan~ola. Escuela Sindical
  - Item 5: Situacion Juridica del Trabajador en la Empresa, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Ciudades Residenciales de la OrganizacionFamiliares del Trabajador, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Ciudades Residenciales de la OrganizacionFamiliares del Trabajador, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: El Parque Sindical Deportivo Puerta de Hierro, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: El Parque Sindical Deportivo Puerta de Hierro, 1961; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Box: 23, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Los Convenios Colectivos Sindicales en el Sector Agrario, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Los Convenios Colectivos Sindicales en el Sector Agrario, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Modificaciones al Reglamento Nacionalde 23 de Diciembre de 1952, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Normas Reglamentarias del DecretoEnfermedades Profesionales, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Reglamento Nacional de Trabajo en las Industrias del Corcho, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Reglamento Nacional de Trabajos Portuarios, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Texto Articulado de la Ley de Ordenacion de a Emigracion, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Escuela Sindical Superior de Hosteleria, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: Espana Semanal: Proyecto de Ley Sindical, 1962; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
    Notes: serial (1 issue)
- Box: 24, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Menu, 1960; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Notes of proceedings of the fourth day's sitting of the second session of the Boad of Enquiry into the Printing Trade appointed under the Trade Disputes (Arbitration and Enquiry) Law, Chapter 386 of the Laws of Jamaica (Revised Edition), 1953, held at the, 1960; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Author: Jamaica. Board of Enquiry into Labour Disputes Between Trade Unions
  - Item 3: Notes of proceedings of the third day's sitting of the second session of the Boad of Enquiry into the Printing Trade appointed under the Trade Disputes (Arbitration and Enquiry) Law, Chapter 386 of the Laws of Jamaica (Revised Edition), 1953, held at the, 1960; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Report of Jamaica on the Inter-RelationshipsAgencies and Services, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: correspondence
  - Item 5: The Report of the Board of Enquiry on the Printing Industry of Jamaica, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Alumina from Jamaica, 1959; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: advertisement
  - Item 7: University College of the West Indies, 1962; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Notes: report
  - Item 8: University College of the West Indies, 1962; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Box: 24, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution and Conditions of Membership, 1953; Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Banana Cultivation Joint Industrial Council, 1957; Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Constitution of the Joint Industrial CouncilConstruction Industry, 1953; Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Joint Industrial Council: Printing Industry, 1956; Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Labour/Management Agreement betweenConstruction Industry, 1956; Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Notes of proceedings of the first day's sitting of the second session of the Boad of Enquiry into the Printing Trade appointed under the Trade Disputes (Arbitration and Enquiry) Law, Chapter 386 of the Laws of Jamaica (Revised Edition), 1953, held at the, 1960; Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Notes of proceedings of the second day's sitting of the second session of the Boad of Enquiry into the Printing Trade appointed under the Trade Disputes (Arbitration and Enquiry) Law, Chapter 386 of the Laws of Jamaica (Revised Edition), 1953, held at the, 1960; Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Notes of proceedings of the third day's sitting of the second session of the Boad of Enquiry into the Printing Trade appointed under the Trade Disputes (Arbitration and Enquiry) Law, Chapter 386 of the Laws of Jamaica (Revised Edition), 1953, held at the, 1960; Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Jamaica: An Economic Survey, 1965; Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Author: Barclays Bank (Dominion, Colonial, and Overseas)
- Box: 24, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Arbitration Proceedings in Connection withNational Workers Union, 1960; Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Notes of proceedings of the fifth day's sitting of the Boad of Enquiry into the Printing Trade appointed under the Trade Disputes (Arbitration and Enquiry) Law, Chapter 386 of the Laws of Jamaica (Revised Edition), 1953, held at the Ministry of Labour, 11, 1960; Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Notes of proceedings of the first day's sitting of the Boad of Enquiry into the Printing Trade appointed under the Trade Disputes (Arbitration and Enquiry) Law, Chapter 386 of the Laws of Jamaica (Revised Edition), 1953, held at the Ministry of Labour, 11, 1960; Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Notes of proceedings of the second day's sitting of the Boad of Enquiry into the Printing Trade appointed under the Trade Disputes (Arbitration and Enquiry) Law, Chapter 386 of the Laws of Jamaica (Revised Edition), 1953, held at the Ministry of Labour, 1, 1960; Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Box: 24, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)